

**Javascript Developer** specializing in front end development. Experienced with many stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous tehnologies including React.js, Vue.js, Node.js, etc.

Phone:

+38164 50 66 848

E-Mail:

jovanvuceljic@gmail.com

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/jovan-vuceljic/

**Portfolio:** 

jovanvuceljic.github.io/portfolio/

## **Skill Highlights**

- React.js
- Vue.js
- Node.js
- Meteor.js
- Git
- MongoDB
- HTML5/CSS3
- Sass/Less

## Languages

- Serbian
- English

# **Experience**

04/2018 - 04/2021

### Digital Mind d.o.o. Belgrade

- Platform development
- Web and mobile software developlent
- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.

2015 - now

#### Freelance

- Building and maintaining web and mobile apps and websites
- Digital products and marketing

## **Education**

2011 -

Bachelor of science –
University of Belgrade Faculty of Mathematics

2014 - 2021

Bachelor of Electrical and Computer Engineering – Academy of Technical and Art Applied Studies Belgrade

### **About me**

I am passionate about developing utilities that can help people irrespective of its age and capabilities. My areas of interest are User Experience, Web and Mobile Development. Love to spend my spare time in identifying the solutions of challenging problems. For me, programming is a way of thinking.